拱顶石汽车旅馆
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
presisco
翻译
零玖/presisco
校对
presisco
特效
压制
presisco
珍珠!你最近去哪了?
Pearl! Where've you been?
...找橄榄石啊
Looking for Peridot.
也就几这几天
For a few days straight.
史蒂文,我知道我也许...
Steven, I know I might have...
让你们,失望了
Disappointed all of you.
我知道石榴还在生我的气,
I know Garnet's very upset with me.
但我要向她证明她可以再次信任我
But I'm going to prove to her that she can trust me again.
噢,石榴!我刚刚在寻找橄榄石哦!
Oh, Garnet! I was just looking for Peridot!
她肯定在什么地方,对吧?
She's bound to be somewhere, right?
有什么新想法吗?
Any new ideas?
我对不起
I'm sorry.
谁想参加公路自驾游?!
Who wants to go on a road trip?!
呃...我来的不是时候?
Um...Is this a bad time?
不,请继续
No. Please continue.
好吧,我要开车去隔壁州-拱顶石
Well, I gotta drive over to the next state, keystone.
你指,拱顶石州?
You mean, the keystone state?
没错,那个州就叫"拱顶石"
Right, the state named keystone.
“拱顶石州”对应现实中的宾夕法尼亚州。格雷格手中册子上的轮廓与宾夕法尼亚州相近，
且宾夕法尼亚处于最初的13个殖民地中央，曾被称为“The Keystone State”。
我在网上的留言板认识了一个人
I met a guy on an Internet message board
卖的洗车用的刷子简直白菜价!
who's selling car-wash brushes for real cheap!
我只需要到拱顶石州跟他碰头并拿货就好
I just gotta meet him in keystone and pick 'em up.
我不喜欢那种刷子,用来洗毛发时总感觉怪怪的
I don't like those brushes. They feel weird on your fur.
详见第一季第6集 Cat Fingers
那么,你喜欢汽车旅馆吗?
Well, do you like motels?
很可能哦!
Probably!
你愿意在汽车旅馆里
Think you'd like to stay at a motel
陪你最喜欢的老爸吗?
with your favorite dad?
我不觉得你是我的最爱哦...
I don't know if you're my favorite...
啊?
What? Huh?
哦,你个崽子,给我过来
Oh, you kidder. Come here.
我等不及享受客房服务了!
I can't wait to get room service!
你想的是"饭店"
You're thinking of a hotel.
我们要去的是"汽车旅馆"
We're going to a motel!
那里有泳池和免费冰块
It'll have a pool and free ice.
而且它就在全世界最好的餐厅旁边!
And it's right next to the best diner in the world!
我也要去
I'm coming, too.
啊?
What?
更好了!
Even better!
嘿,石榴,我知道我有点过度渲染了
Hey, Garnet, I know I'm talking this place up,
其实没听上去那么好
but it ain't exactly the ritz.
“the ritz”可能指的是伦敦的五星级酒店The Ritz hotel(利兹酒店)
我自己会做判断的
I'll be the judge of that.
那么,这样的话...公路旅行!
Well, in that case... Road trip!
公路旅行!
Road trip!
公路旅行
Road trip.
好极了!
Wonderful!
我会确保紫晶知道要...
I'll make sure Amethyst knows that...
好吧
Fine.
那么...再见
Well, goodbye.
这会很有趣,对吧,老爸?
This is gonna be fun, right, dad?
现实中也有一家“Keystone Motel”，坐落于St. Pete Beach, Florida。
那家汽车旅馆曾被宇宙小子的粉丝们恶搞过——有人在Google Plus上
留下差评，称"马桶被冻住了""披萨是方形的""游泳池被完全蒸发"之类的。
另一个汽车旅馆的优势-
Another great thing about motels --
你能直接开到客房门前!
you can drive right up to your door!
我要在泳池里畅游,点播一部大片,享受免费冰块!
I'm gonna swim in the pool, order a movie, get free ice!
这次一定会超赞的!
It's gonna be great!
之前先让我检查一下有没有床虱啊!
Not before we check for bedbugs, it isn't!
Mm.
好消息!没有床虱!
Good news! We're bugless!
喔,有消息了
Oop, that's my cue.
嘿,你不介意在我回来前"守住城堡"吗?
Hey, do you mind holding down the fort till I get back?
好,那我去和卖隧道刷的人碰面了
Great. I'm off to see a man about a tunnel brush.
格雷格此处的话是“see a man about a dog/horse”的变种。
原话从对比赛下注的委婉表达，演变成为避免流露真实原因，用来结束对话的用语
一个网友
An Internet man.
如果一小时内我没回来,记得报警
If I'm not back in an hour, call the police.
格雷格此处的话是“If I'm not back [soon], call the police”的变种
这里应该是致敬默片时代的Keystone Kops
好～的!
Oh-kay!
跟我一起蹦吧,石榴!
Bounce with me, Garnet!
或-或者我们也可以看看宣传册子
O-or we could look at brochures.
噢～拱顶石洞穴
Ooh, keystone caverns.
“Keystone Caverns”可能指的是“Crystal Cave”；“Crystal Cave”是宾夕法尼亚州东南部的一处自然景观。
要冷静
Calm down.
我不想原谅珍珠!
I don't feel like forgiving Pearl!
我不理解
Don't understand
我们必须要!
we must!
如果你不想听,你可以离开啊!
If you're not going to listen, then you can just go!
我们必须放下这件事,红宝石
We must move past this, Ruby.
她向我们撒谎,好让我们组成红玛瑙!
She lied to us so we'd form sardonyx!
她骗了我们!你不觉得被利用了吗?
She tricked us! Don't you feel used?!
红宝石!蓝宝石!我-
Ruby! Sapphire! I --
你选择将这件事过度抬高
you're choosing to take it personally.
这是融合,蓝宝石!
It's fusion, Sapphire!
还有什么对于我们,相比融合,更重要?!
What's more personal to us than fusion?!
我知道你仍然很生气
I know you're still upset.
哦,所以只是我喽?
Oh, so it's just me?
当然不是
Of course not.
你难道看不出我完全被愤怒吞没了?
Can't you see I'm completely engulfed with rage?
那么,我怎么感觉不到 ?!
Well, it doesn't feel like it!
我们越早原谅珍珠,
The sooner we forgive Pearl,
对我们所有人都越好
the better it will be for us all.
你,并非,层次更高,像,你,自以为,那样!
You're not as above this as you think you are!
没错,我就是
Yes, I am.
你不可能永远生她的气
You can't stay angry with her forever.
想赌赌吗?
Wanna bet?
红宝石,注意地毯,
Ruby, the carpet.
你-我都不能-啊!
You -- I can't even -- ugh!
很高兴,再次见到你?
Nice to see you again?
很高兴见到你
Nice to see you, too.
嘿,红宝石
Hey, Ruby.
你想在泳池里游泳吗?
You wanna swim in the pool?
这可是融合,史蒂文!
It's fusion, Steven!
感觉蓝宝石根本就不在乎!
It's like Sapphire doesn't even care!
"而且我们应该用'成年人'的视角看问题"
And we're supposed to be the bigger gem about this.
我们,一,直,是,"成年人"!
We're always the bigger gem!
那么,不行!这次不行!这件事!不行!
Well, not this time! Not about this!
来吧,为什么不在泳池里先冷静一下呢?
Come on, why don't you come cool down in the pool?
我,才不需要冷-静呢!
I don't need to cool down!
快啊,红宝石,水很爽～哦!
Come on, Ruby. The water's nice!
为什么她,总是,表现的像,我才是,荒谬的一方?
Why does she always act like I'm being ridiculous?
就只因为她想伪装成
Just because she wants to pretend
自己没有感情一样
that she doesn't have feelings?!
红宝石?
Ruby?
你把泳池变成温泉了!
You made a warm spot!
啊!是"烫泉"了!
Ah! A hot spot!
水开了!
Boiling!
呃,我还是回屋吧
Uh, I'm gonna go back to the room.
蓝宝石?
Sapphire?
你好,史蒂文
Hello, Steven.
你-你...还-还-还好吗?
A-are you... D-d-doin' okay?
我-很-好
I'm fine.
好-吧
O-okay.
想-想一起看电视吗?
W-wanna watch TV together?
可以
Sure.
哈,频道的号码都乱了
Huh. The channels are all the wrong numbers.
嘿～你能用你的预知能力
Hey, can you use your future powers
预测一下我最喜欢的频道吗?
to predict what channel I'd love the most?
嗯...43,但也没什么
Hmm...43. But there's not much on.
宾夕法尼亚州的43频道为标清Nickelodeon(尼克)台
Nickelodeon为Cartoon Network(卡通网络，”宇宙小子“的东家)的竞争对手
嘿,蓝宝石...
Hey, Sapphire...
即使我这样做,红宝石也不会听的
Even if I do, Ruby won't listen.
蛤?
Huh?
你会说我该和红宝石谈谈
You're going to say I should talk to Ruby,
但这没用
but it won't help.
但-但她看起来非常生气
B-but she seems really upset.
这无关紧要
That doesn't matter.
她不可能永远生珍珠的气,
We can't stay mad at Pearl forever,
而且她也不可能永远生我的气,
and she can't stay mad at me forever.
而且之后她会回心转意并发现我是对的
And then she'll come back and see that I'm right.
你-你-你确-确-确定?
A-a-are you s-sure?
我能看到命运的轨迹一路延伸到时间的地平线
I can see the path of fate as it stretches toward the horizon.
红宝石躲避不了宿命
Ruby can't avoid the inevitable.
她只是在让自己的情绪失控
She's just letting her emotions get out of hand.
你不是吗?
N-n-not you, though?
当然
No.
我...得去卫生间了
I'm...Going to the bathroom.
同样无法避免
Also inevitable.
蓝宝石?
Sapphire?
马桶冻住了
The toilet's frozen.
这就是命啊
Such is fate.
那我也注定要去外面的草地上尿了?
Am I fated to pee outside on the grass, too?
是的
Yes.
拱顶石州...
"Keystone state"...
嘿,小子,我带晚餐了哦
Hey, stu-ball, I brought dinner.
嘿,老爸,怎么样?
Hey, dad. How'd it go?
呃,他以前不是个凶手,这还不错
Well, he wasn't an ex-murderer, so that was good.
你穿着浴衣在外面干什么?
What are you doing outside in your bathing suit?
而且石榴在哪?
And where's Garnet?
他不会喜欢方形
He's not going to like that it's square.
哦,天哪,另一个呢?
Oh, boy. Where's the other one?
她在原来是泳池的地方散步呢
She's pacing around in what used to be the pool.
有些非常严重的事情发生了
Something pretty serious must be going on
如果都能让石榴分裂了的话
if it made Garnet split up.
但,嘿,我们仍能高兴起来啊
But hey, we can still have a good time.
方形的披萨?
Square Pizza?!
第二季第2集说好的不介意任何基本形状呢？！
这个疯狂的州怎么了?
What's wrong with this crazy state?!
“方形披萨”可能指的是宾夕法尼亚州东北部非常流行的“Old Forge style pizza”
“Old Forge style pizza”通常使用American cheese
而且通常叫"tray"(盘)和"cut"(块)，而非"pie"(张)和"slice"(片)
儿子,你生命中总有些时候
Son, there'll come a time in your life
得学会接受所有的披萨
when you learn to accept all Pizza.
为什么红宝石和蓝宝石直接,和好呢?
Why can't Ruby and Sapphire just make up?
有的时候相互爱恋的人
Sometimes people that love each other
可能会无意中相互伤害
can hurt each other's feelings without meaning to.
我们应该给他们点空间
We should just give them some space.
但我觉得她们能解决这个问题
But I think they'd work it out
如果她们愿意沟通的话
if they'd just talk to each other.
明天早上一切都会变好的
Everything will be better in the morning.
我们都要去世界上最好的餐厅
We'll all go to the best diner in the world,
她们将吃到世界上最好的早餐
where they'll eat the best breakfast in the world.
你觉得这有用吗?
You think that'll help?
没什么能像早餐一样让人们团聚
Nothing like a little breakfast to bring people together.
你确实是我最喜欢的老爸
You really are my favorite dad.
我就知道这份披萨能帮到我
I knew this Pizza would put me over the top.
世界上
最好的
餐厅
嘿!
Hey!
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢!
Thanks!
怎么了?不饿吗?
What's the matter? Not hungry?
宝石人不用吃饭,爸爸
Gems don't need to eat, dad.
呃,石榴有时会吃啊
Eh, Garnet likes to eat sometimes.
啊!显然,石榴,不,在!
Ugh! Well, Garnet's not here!
唔,我的天!
Mmm. Oh, boy!
这-真的是-世界上-最好的餐厅!
This really is the best diner in the world!
你在晃桌子
You're shaking the table.
噢?!哈!
Oh?! Heh!
我,很好奇你居然还,有点感情,说实话!
I'm kinda surprised you felt anything at all, to be honest!
我-不需要-感觉,我能看到
I didn't need to feel -- I saw.
所,有,事你都,看,得,一清,二楚,不,是,吗?!
Everything's just so crystal clear to you, isn't it?!
这会过去了
This will pass.
她迟早会让自己熄火的
She'll eventually just burn herself out.
那是你,的,想,法!
That's what you think!
我是永不熄灭的烈焰,baby!
I am an eternal flame, baby!
你又不了解我!
You don't know me!
我怎么可能不了解
How could I possibly not know you
你看看你!嗷～嚎-嚎
Look at you! Awww-haw-haw.
我们总是融合在一起
we always fused.
嘿,这没什么,伙计!
Hey, it's okay, pal!
看看你自己,看看你在干什么...
Look at you. Look at what you're going on about...
你都不了解你自己!哈!
You don't even know yourself! Hah!
我们仍然能解决的!
We can still save this!
我们为什么不讲这些打包带走然后-
Why don't we just bag these up to go and --
噢,天哪
ah, geez.
史蒂文!
Steven!
当石榴说她要和我与爸爸
I was so happy when Garnet said
一起旅行时我还很高兴!
she was gonna come on this trip with me and dad!
家里糟透了,这里也糟透了!
Home's been awful. Here's been awful!
我以为你们想放松一下
I thought you wanted to have a fun time,
但每个人也都表现的非常糟糕!
but everyone's been acting awful, too!
这种氛围-这种氛围一直跟着我们
It -- it just came with us.
我就不理解了,是-这是因为我吗?
I don't understand. Is it -- is it me?
不!
No!Uh,
史蒂文,都是我们的错!
Steven, it's all us!
但我们让他感觉这都是他的错
But we made him feel like it was his fault.
我总是关注着未来
I keep looking into the future
那时这一切都已经被解决了
when all of this has already been solved,
就好像你当下的感受毫无意义一样
as if it doesn't matter how you feel in the present.
难怪-你觉得-我毫不-在乎!
No wonder you think I don't care!
蓝宝石!
Sapphire!
不,不不不不!
No, no, no, no, no!
这都是我的错!
This is all my fault!
我-我并不想寻找解决方法
I-I didn't want to look for a solution.
我只是在犯孩子气而已
I just wanted to be mad.
你是对的,你一直是对的
You're right. You're always right.
我之前犯傻了
I was being stupid.
我不觉得你笨!
I don't think you're stupid!
我,对不起
I'm,sorry.
你真的认为我对已经发生的毫不在意?
You honestly think I'm not upset about what happened?
我-只是试着做正确的事而已
I was just trying to do the right thing.
我知道
I know.
你知道分开的好处是什么吗?
You know what's nice about being split up?
是什么?
What?
我能看到你了
I get to look at you.
噗!
Pfft!
严肃点!
Be serious!
这才是我的爱笑的小蓝嘛!
There's my laffy saffy!
嘘!你这是在史蒂文面前放闪光弹啊!
Shh! You're embarrassing me in front of Steven!
那么,我为早餐付过钱了...
Well, I paid for breakfast...
还有桌子损坏的费用
And the damage to the booth.
不管怎么说,我觉得我放够假了
Anyhoo, I think I'm all vacationed out.
准备好收拾东西了吗?
Ready to call it a day?
先得拿到免费冰块再说!
Not before we get our free ice!
石榴!
Garnet!
我们到家～啦!
We're home!
我不知道为什么我总是-
I just don't know why I keep--
哦!呃-你们看起来过得很开心啊
Oh!Ah-you look like you all had fun.
是啊,问题解决了!
Yeah, it all worked out!
石榴,你感觉怎么样?
Garnet, how are you?
不是现在
Not now.
她总算又和我说话了...算是
She's speaking to me again...Kind of.
那真是一次超棒的旅行
That really was a great trip.
我们能再去一次吗?
Can we go back?
也许吧...
Maybe one day... But not to that diner.
但-不算那家餐馆
But not to that diner.
哦,天哪
Oh, boy.
你
♪ You
爱,如你
♪ love like you